This is the Amanda Seals show on this Tuesday.
What's happening, man? Nails right here.
That is Amanda Seals.
It is time for the big up letdown.
Amanda's about to salute somebody.
Scottish actor Alan Cumming announced that he has handed back the OBE award that he received 14 years ago.
Now, in England, the British Isles, the United Kingdom, the award is given from the monarchy.
And he won his award for his activism for equal rights for the gay and lesbian community in the USA.
Now, for those who don't know, Alan Cumming is like a very well-known actor.
And like he won the Tony Award for his performance in Cabaret on Broadway.
And he's just like an incredible performer.
So he was not being honored for his performing.
He was being honored for his activism.
But he now says, and this is why he's getting the big up.
He says he's returning his award because since the conversations around the monarchy that popped up after the queen died,
regarding the way the British Empire profited at the expense and death of indigenous peoples, it opened his eyes.
And he said he doesn't feel comfortable having this award from a monarchy that committed these acts.
Yes.
And so just so you know, OBE stands for the Order of the British Empire.
But I'm always going to show love and give a for a co-conspirator, particularly a white person who finds out the truth and moves accordingly with that information.